<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Alic&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.michael-korsoutlet.top/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Alic&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 09:34:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.michael-korsoutlet.top/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thinking of Guan Chengjun</title>
      <link>https://www.michael-korsoutlet.top/posts/462/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 09:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.michael-korsoutlet.top/posts/462/</guid>
      <description>When I got up in the morning, I opened my computer. Inadvertently into Li Danyuan&amp;rsquo;s QQ space, in his album saw a photo of Guan Chengjun - much more handsome than before, the gods, a manly man!
It seems that I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen him for years, and I don&amp;rsquo;t know where he is now working in where he is developed, I don&amp;rsquo;t know anything about him now. As if the only remaining little friendship between classmates is also so difficult to touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legends</title>
      <link>https://www.michael-korsoutlet.top/posts/463/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 09:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.michael-korsoutlet.top/posts/463/</guid>
      <description>The cloud fell deeply in love with the sky from the day it saw it.
Cloud said that the sky was a myth in her heart and she could not resist the power of God.
So she said to the sky, &amp;ldquo;I love you! Love your brilliant blue!&amp;rdquo;
The sky smiles, &amp;ldquo;I belong to all things and cannot be attributed to your love.&amp;rdquo;
The sea is also deeply in love with clouds from the day it sees them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The first time in life to use the health insurance card Experience first-class face authentication is scary</title>
      <link>https://www.michael-korsoutlet.top/posts/yibaodiyici/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 13:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.michael-korsoutlet.top/posts/yibaodiyici/</guid>
      <description>Thu, 07 Oct 2020 17:55:17
The first time in my life was given to Dasenlin Three days ago, on the eighteenth day of the eighth month of the lunar calendar, the night was dark and windy, so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stand it and went out, planning to find a famous pharmacy to purchase a panacea&amp;hellip;
A week ago two hands a little back of the tiger mouth for some reason, some small rash, a little itchy, sometimes red, sometimes not so red, sometimes more raised, sometimes more flat, for this small problem, I never endure, and wait for it to heal on its own.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
